♪ ~
Date night, kids.
I wonder if it's already spring break today.
This is Onagawa Station, a short walk from Onagawa Station, and this is the ocean.
Hello, everyone, I'm back in Onagawa.
Onagawa, we call them our friends and we get along well with them, but...
Later on, but he's still pretty young, so he fell into it from there. ogato
I've been coming here for a while, but I haven't been able to visit recently.
And I'm currently working on a play called "In the Best House" to rave reviews.
We are currently performing, but tomorrow we have a performance in Sendai, and since we are in Sendai, we thought we would go to Onagawa as well, so we came to greet the people of Onagawa.
yay
Whenever we came to Onagawa, even Takahashi-san and Takamasa-san from Onagawa would say "welcome home" and the people in town would say "welcome home" too.
It really is like a second home to me, and I love it because it's a warm town, but today I have time to relax.
I'd like to take a walk in Onagawa and hopefully eat some good food.
then
Let's get right to it, shall we?
Last time, I think, was with Ms. Karen from Iginari Tohoku.
Come here. That thing, you know, the tile I designed.
You mentioned something about it being put up, but I don't know where it is.
The director and the director of the current stage production are both from Onagawa.
I feel we have a connection, and I'd like to share some of that with you.
bowl of rice topped with seafood and vegetables
Where should we go?
I'm not really sure what the story of the play I'm working on is, so it's up to each person to decide how they feel about it, but I just can't help but think that it's a very interesting play.
There are many scenes that are covered with the city of Onagawa.
Even the last part of the story seems to be just like Konagawara's.
In my mind.
That's why you don't have any sets at practice or anything like that.
When you start reading a script, it can be quite complicated.
It was hard for me to imagine what it would be like.
I'm in the town of Koyonagawa, just down the street here.
Straight ahead, there was the ocean.
There was an ocean.
People used to live here, and there used to be a shopping district, and all kinds of things.
This is the kind of situation we're in now.
I'm trying to create a square, a picture, where everyone can come together.
I was practicing while imagining
It feels like a strange picture, doesn't it?
what's more
This play really has a lot of links to me.
I'm trying to imagine the town of Onagawa, where we've been getting along so well, and so on.
The director is from Onagawa.
I wondered why the director knew so much about me.
The stories are linked.
I think the stage will probably be finished by the time this airs.
I'm probably saying this somewhere else.
It's getting to be the second half of the stage and then again.
Thus, there are many facts that come to light.
I played the role of Shizuku in the play.
Well, I found a chart of my great-grandmother's family register from my great-grandmother's house.
I had a drop in my family.
And the letters are exactly the same.
And I'm really surprised right now.
There's a yellow post in the stage.
I have a yellow post.
What? Really?
I have goosebumps. There's a clock tower.
Do you have a link like this?
I'm Taro Natsu.
be surprised
Oh, my God, really. Why so many?
In such a short period of time.
But that's great.
Thank God you found it.
Because I didn't notice. I didn't notice.
Hey, he said it's a yellow postbox for happiness.
I'm a little touched and moved, I mean, I've got goosebumps.
A little bit this way and it's already the ocean.
I'm a little bit on the edge.
I don't know what to do.
Then last time.
Suddenly, Mr. Tohoku and Karen-kun.
When I came here when I came here.
I changed the tiles, and now that I've seen those tiles, I remember.
that being so
Yes, sir.
Well, I don't know, maybe we could look for it, or maybe we could just go to the store.
Shall we go say hello and ask a few questions?
Great. I remember when my heart was here.
I turned the corner of the cat and...
This is it... the Port Town Ceramica Studio Spanish Tile.
abbr. of particle "ni" (used especially when it precedes the verb "naru")
Hello. - Hello.
Excuse me for interrupting.
You have a visitor.
dear
You wrote this.
I kind of forgot what I wrote.
Karen's.
I remember the tiles.
Hello. - Hello.
Ah! Anpan!
dear
Oh man, I knew I was going to have to do this pants thing.
Karen-kun's.
Yes I wrote Mr. Monanav.
I heard these tiles are going to be put up somewhere.
Yes, I think there are actually a lot of memorial tiles on it.
I'm planning to install it there.
But I've had fans come to see me.
We will actually make the same tiles.
Mr. Monanav, have you been here quite a bit?
Take a picture with me.
I see.
But I'm glad to have it displayed in the store like this.
Thank you.
It's been a while since I visited Onagawa again, so I came to say hello.
thank you for your help on this occasion
I see Mr. Monanav is here too.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back slowly.
Glad to hear it.
And that means they're decorating the store.
Mononofu also came to visit us.
The same tile design?
Next time, Mr. Mononoff.
mononoff
I'd like to see the tiles in the design, though.
But once through this city.
Another round.
A little bit.
There are so many things I don't understand on my own.
That one.
I'd love to come see you.
Come to Onagawa!
If you said you were going to meet him, he's the only one you're going to see.
Now, by the way, do you all know where you are?
Here we are at Mr. Takamasa, who has been a great help to us.
This one or this one?
clash
Now then, I would like to go see Mr. Takahashi of Takamasa as soon as possible!
I guess it's been a little while.
ahit-hello
Welcome back, Mr. Takahashi.
I'm home!
I am performing a play called "The Best Runaway" in Sendai tomorrow.
Tomorrow is the Sendai show, so I thought I'd like to go say hello to the woman's side.
I came to see Mr. Takahashi.
Thank you.
Thank you for stopping by on such short notice.
The factory where all of you are who can't open it.
I have to come here to get started, so I've been taking care of you a lot, Mr. Takamasa, since I first came to the women's side.
That's a long time, and thanks for the real involvement with the women's side.
I felt a great connection with the director of the play, Mr. Miura.
I was from the women's side.
seriously
Okay, so...
Where's Mr. Miura?
His name is Naoyuki Miura, and he says he's from the women's side.
There's a limited number of Miuras on the women's side.
I am still going to Sendai, so I feel very special to be able to perform in Sendai this time.
I'm very attached to it, and I've been doing this for a long time, so...
I'm feeling a little bit of that kind of connection today.
Our Miura is taking care of us.
So I went and toured our factory.
Lathyrus quinquenervius (species of vetchling)
I've been watching from up there.
That's right, you showed me.
Prolonging is just now beginning.
I could see it.
It's just starting now.
Sasakamas are cute!
So now it's like soft serve ice cream.
grunting or groaning sound
You said "loose."
There.
This will be the seed of the sasakamo.
Okay, here we are.
full of seeds
Cute little aligned Sasakamo's.
Something is already made.
It's a trial run.
trying out a new sword or blade (originally on someone, but now on soaked straw targets)
And from the Sasakamo in the back.
They were large sized mini Kamabokos.
that far away
cute
baby
The one in the back.
It's like they sell it at convenience stores all the time.
Mr. Takamasa's stuff is sold, isn't it?
oh, yes!
something (or someone) that one has missed for a long time
remember
I remember being impressed even then.
When I was given a tour of the factory.
How's it going?
Something from then on and from then on.
There were changes at the factory.
Like changes in products.
that's so, isn't it
Product Development
We're putting a lot of effort into it.
since then
Take the Emperor's Tile.
Rinsui's
He won the Minister's Award and other awards.
in Tokyo
Many thanks for all you've done.
You won an award.
That's great.
Evolving more and more
But I forgot the type of product or whatever.
also
I don't know what's going on.
A lot of them came out.
what does that mean?
What's selling now?
Smoked cheese and bacon is what they're selling.
That is absolutely delicious.
A little bit stylish.
Absolutely delicious!
May I also take a tour of the store?
If you'd like.
something that has happened non-stop
This area is a product made by a company within the town of Onaga.
Wow, huh?
Oh no, I want to buy some fillets.
But over here...
I'll definitely buy it, I'll buy it today and go home.
Savory bacon
Maybe I've never seen something like this around here before.
oh, yes!
Wow, this is delicious!
I bought this.
This is the one I mentioned earlier.
Smoked cheese & bacon
Wow, let's buy some and go home.
Looks delicious.
I really like this type of products.
Oh, Gozen kamaboko. Yes.
Kamaboko, you know, it's a little boring just to look at it.
Yes. Shall we do the Zelkova experience?
I want to do it! After all these years! It's been a while.
We've done it here before.
Oh! There's a picture on the wall! From those days! I miss it! It really brings back memories!
2019?
It was at Compaqa, wasn't it?
I miss it so much.
I'm looking forward to it!
Put down the sasakanago!
Ah! Here it comes! Thank you!
Can I put two bottles down for now?
Wow! Thank you!
Can I leave three bottles here for a moment?
There is a trick to baking sasa-kamaboko for this.
What is it?
You only have to turn it over once.
Really? I shouldn't have done it so many times.
It's better not to have many times.
I do that a lot when I go out for yakiniku.
I just wanted to tinker with it.
In the case of barbequed meat, blood will float in the air.
I'd prefer to heat that up.
When you grill fish, you only turn it over once.
something like
I've done this a lot of times.
The surface goes light before the bones attach.
Is that so?
I'm going to be rich.
You only have to turn it over once.
Yes, it is. It's a pretty good shade.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
ah!
Bijoux is nice. Bijoux is the best.
Looks good. Last year.
When you come to us.
Onagawa bar. Karen's there.
We were shocked when he said he didn't like the bijoux.
He said something about how the young people of today use these words.
I like the bijoux, like your wife. You remember it very well. I remember it, I remember it.
Bijoux is good. I'm sure he said that.
Bijoux Nice color
I will take it. Now then.
It's hot. Be careful.
insanely hot
Because it's about 30,000 degrees hotter.
hot (thing)
Delicious, really delicious, the flavor of the fish spreads the moment you bite into it!
The baking process adds a savory flavor to the food.
The meat itself has the sweetness of the fish, and the sweetness mixed with this savory flavor makes it very soft and fluffy.
It's like a futon. It's that soft and sticky.
Delicious. I'm a food report master.
I really want to eat this every day for a 3 o'clock snack.
Much, but I used to get them to eat it as a snack.
Children are eating less and less local fish cake as a snack.
It's definitely better to eat this than some weird candy, and I think it's good for you too.
They use local fish.
I think it's a very good thing... for the local Onagawa children.
Thanks to you, I'm used to it. I really am.
Like buying a piece of fish cake at our store with 100 yen or 150 yen in your pocket.
It's a luxurious treat. They sell it at the convenience store.
And then he buys our stuff. That's extravagant.
Thank you for the food, it was so delicious!
Thank you very much. I'm not quite there yet.
I think I want to enjoy Onagawa.
Do you have any other recommendations?
I mentioned before that supermarkets are back in Onagawa.
You haven't sold it yet. That's right.
I've been thinking about it for a while, but I'm a super fan.
Since Mr. Takahashi mentioned it before, what kind of
And I'm a sucker for cheap, so I'm curious to know what kind of supermarket it is.
We're all weak. We all have power.
It's a power word. It's a power word.
Well, let's go there, okay? Okay? Take me there.
Then let's go.